{"status":"Success","data":{"quiz_datas":[{"question_no":"413","question":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b","option1":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d38\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d48\u0d24\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d17\u0d32\u0d40\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b \u0d17\u0d32\u0d40\u0d32\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"698","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u200c \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c \u0d30\u0d02\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1c\u0d40\u200d\u0d35\u0d4d\u200c \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u200c \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d\u200c \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d30\u0d02\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u200c \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d?","option1":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2b\u0d4d\u200c\r\n","option2":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c","option4":"\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"199","question":"\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d36\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?","option1":"4","option2":"5","option3":"6","option4":"3","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"497","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35","option2":"\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"251","question":"2015 \u2013\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d6a \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f?","option1":"\u0d06\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d06\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02","option3":"\u0d06\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02","option4":"\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"72","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d48\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"2.209 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d","option2":"1.609 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d","option3":"2.609 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d","option4":"1.209 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"587","question":"\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d21\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7d","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"619","question":"\u0d2f\u0d41.\u0d0e\u0d7b.\u0d06\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d27 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d","option1":"OPCW","option2":"CWBTO","option3":"OPEC","option4":"IUCN","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"539","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d2c\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d24\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 (1978)","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7e (2006)","option3":"\u0d13\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 (1970)","option4":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f (1996)","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"563","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d02","option2":"\u0d36\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7a","option4":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"1"}]},"code":"100"}